Contact

yashup1997@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ yashupadhyay1997 (LinkedIn) aigotneuralmind.wordpress.com/ (Blog)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Artificial Intelligence (AI)
Computer Vision

Certifications

Deep Learning and NLP A-Z: How to create a ChatBot

Python for Data Science

Publications

Comparative analysis of feature selection in epilepsy seizure recognition using cuckoo, gravitational search and bat algorithm

Optimized Model for Cervical Cancer Detection Using Binary Cuckoo Search

Deep Refinement: Capsule Network With Attention Mechanism Based System For Text Classification

Optical Character Recognition with Convolutional Neural Network

Yash Upadhyay

Kaggle Competition Expert || Actively looking for full-time opportunities in Data science

New Delhi

Summary

Researcher with keen interest in taking on problems related to machine learning and Al. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), machine learning, C++, Google Cloud Platform, and Java. Strong engineering professional pursuing B.Tech focused in Computer Science from bharati vidyapeeth's college of engineering.

Experience

NAYAN INDIA TECHNOLOGIES

Junior Software Engineer, Artificial Intelligence April 2019 - August 2019 (5 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Towards Data Science Contributing Writer March 2019 - August 2019 (6 months)

Gamut Analytics
Al content developer
December 2018 - February 2019 (3 months)

Defence Research and Development Organisation Summer Trainee June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Education

bhartiye vidyapeeth's college of engineering Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)